VAN THIEU NGUYEN

Frontend Developer



Contact Information

- May 07, 1997
- Male
- A Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam
- 0363091909
- in vanthieu-nguyen
- Curriculum Vitae
- Curriculum Vitae Github

Skills

Technical Skills

React, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Redux Toolkit Query, Next, Ant Design, Cypress, Jquery, CSS/SCSS, Responsive.

Soft Skills

- Teamwork
- Time management
- Communication
- Problem solving

Language

Vietnamese, English

Objective

As a consistent, hard-working, highly motivated person, I am looking forward to participating as a team member in a dynamic work environment which provides an opportunity to make a strong contribution by utilizing and expanding upon related education, skills, experiences, and capabilities.

Work experience

Frontend Developer

Mar 2022 - Present

Shopback

- Maintain, revamp UI/UX and implement new features in Back Office for ten countries.

Frontend Developer

Jan 2020 - Mar 2022

Shopee

- Build many services to serve local Vietnam operations, such as Game Admin, Warehouse, Flash Sale, Seller Rewards,... (Single SPA, React, Redux, Ant).
- Build landing page website for Seller Rewards program (Next, React, Redux, Responsive).
- Research and build a cross-platform desktop app that supports Windows/macOS. Shopee operators can create a carousel banner, a campaign calendar, a drawing tool,... (Electron, React, Redux, Ant, React Final Form).
- Build game "Số gì đây?": Create an admin page on Shopee Desktop App to set up data and images, import attendees, Handle logic to randomize the winner based on certain criteria (React, Redux, Ant, Broadcast Channel API).
- Research and write integration testing (Cypress).
- Suggestions to improve UI to make the product better.
- Organize technical sharing for team members: Sharing about EletronJS and Cypress. Get Shopee reward in Happy Trainers Day.

Javascript Developer

May 2019 - Dec 2019

Gameloft

Interests

- Challenge myself with a new programming language.
- Played some brain-expanding game in free time.
- Traveled somewhere nearby HCM city at the weekend.

- Design interface for the tool on the website using Javascript (Nodejs, React, Redux, Material UI).
- Programming mini-game on Spark AR tool (effect on Facebook and Instagram) (Javascript, Spark AR Tool).
- Optimize, fix bugs and implement new features in old projects.

Game Evolution Programmer Sep 2

Sep 2018 - May 2019

Gameloft

- Check and fix bugs in the game Dragon Mania Legend (C++, Java).
- Implement new features in this game.

Education

Ho Chi Minh city University of Technology

Sep 2015 - Nov 2019

Major: Control Engineering & Automation

GPA: 8.54/10

Honors & Awards

2017-2019: Panasonic Scholarship

@vanthieunguyen